<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Aloys B.</title>
    <link>https://aloysb.xyz/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Aloys B.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.132.1</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:07:37 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://aloysb.xyz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Quickly Open Localhost from Anywhere using Hammerspoon</title>
      <link>https://aloysb.xyz/posts/quickly-open-localhost-from-anywhere-using-hammerspoon/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 17:07:37 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://aloysb.xyz/posts/quickly-open-localhost-from-anywhere-using-hammerspoon/</guid>
      <description>Quickly Open Localhost from Anywhere using Hammerspoon I love to reduce friction in my workflows.
I find it incredibly useful and pleasant.
You might not save hours in your day, but you increase your skills and get a hit of satisfaction every time you use [INSERT THE TOOL YOU BUILT HERE].
It also greatly help you staying in the flow.
As a developer, you have access to some incredible tools that you can leverage improve your workflows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Improved Vertical Scrolling in Neovim</title>
      <link>https://aloysb.xyz/posts/improved-vertical-scrolling-in-neovim/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2024 09:07:37 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://aloysb.xyz/posts/improved-vertical-scrolling-in-neovim/</guid>
      <description>Improved Vertical Scrolling in Neovim Neovim is great.
What I really like about Neovim and similar tools is the fact that you can customize it to fit your workflow, rather than the other way around.
When reading code in Neovim, I often use Ctrl-U/D to scroll vertically through a file.
One minor issue is that you quickly end up with the active line at the top or bottom edge of your window.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Find and Execute Package.json Scripts the Easy Way</title>
      <link>https://aloysb.xyz/posts/find-and-execute-package-json-scripts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2024 09:07:37 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://aloysb.xyz/posts/find-and-execute-package-json-scripts/</guid>
      <description>How to Quickly Find and Execute Scripts in a Large package.json Sometimes, package.json&amp;rsquo;s scripts section gets very long - especially in a monorepo.
Fortunately, fzf + jq makes a great combo to quickly find and execute package.json&amp;rsquo;s scripts.
Prerequisites You will need the following CLI:
jq: a utility to work with JSON files fzf: a powerful, versatile fuzzy finder TL;DR: #!bin/bash # Display the list of npm scripts in a fuzzy finder to execute jq -r &amp;#39;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bulk Archive Github Repositories</title>
      <link>https://aloysb.xyz/posts/bulk-archive-github-repositories/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 17:07:37 +1000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://aloysb.xyz/posts/bulk-archive-github-repositories/</guid>
      <description>Clean Up Your GitHub Profile by Bulk Archiving Repos If you have been on github for more than a few months, you most likely have been accumulating repositories.
While it&amp;rsquo;s great to see your progress, you might not want older, unfinished projects cluttering your profile.
Instead of deleting them and losing your stats, you can archive them.
If you are not embarassed of your former self, you are not growing fast enough.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
